Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Video Editing
Gigglebot
Rael
Zenef
Gigglebot
Rael
Zenef
Timing
Bastia
Gab
Typesetting
PhosCity
Gab
Quality Control
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
TurtlePancake09
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Pepperjack
Scolines
TurtlePancake09
Soundtracking
Halee
Graphics
Datenshi
Karaoke
KaitouYahiko
Subtitle Editing
Zenef
Translation
DemonRin
Funimation
Raws
Neo-Raws
Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode.
Subtitles will likely not function properly.
Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv:
https://mpv.io
Sandy Island
(The Kingdom of Alabasta)
Sir Crocodile, the Pirate
The Port Town of Nanohana
Sir Crocodile...
Crocodile!
Huh?
Ahh... Sir Crocodile!
I knew he'd come!
Crocodile?!
From the Seven Warlords...?
Silence, you fools!
I've only come for that pirate's head!
He's amazing...
He always says that
but saves us anyway!
Hurray for Crocodile!
Alabasta's guardian deity!
Crocodile!
King of the desert! Crocodile!
Sir Crocodile
One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea
Former Bounty: 81 Million Berries
Sir Crocodile
One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea
Former Bounty: 81 Million Berries
Sir Crocodile
One of the Seven Warlords of the Sea
Former Bounty: 81 Million Berries
Well, call me what you will.
Don't just think you can waltz in
and plunder this country, pirates.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Aren't you underestimating us?
You thinking of taking us
all on by yourself?!
You sold out to the authorities,
you government dog!
You think you're some kinda hero?!
Those who wish to live,
lay on the ground.
Is he stupid?! He's wide open!
Get him! He won't keep us
from this town's money and valuables!
– Yeah!
Is this really a famous Warlord?!
I'm a whole different
caliber of pirate, swine.
Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile! Crocodile!
Crocodile again...
Alubarna Palace
Kingdom of Alabasta
He was one step ahead again?
By the time we got to Nanohana,
it was all over.
I see.
Either way, it's fine
as long as the citizens are safe.
Nefertari Cobra
King of Alabasta
We are indebted to him.
There's no mistake.
Our ship is heading to Alabasta.
Luffy! Don't lie!
Tell me what you know.
Hey, why are you looking away?
Look me in the eyes!
Well... um, really...
I don't know anything.
Then answer me this.
For this trip to Alabasta, I carefully procured
and divided enough food for eight people,
so how did it disappear
during the night?
It's pointless to try and fool me!
You've got the worst poker face.
Hey, you have something
around your mouth.
Ah! Shoot! Crumbs?!
It was you!
C'mon...
Ah, Nami... You saw, right?
The large rat trap
just won't do anymore.
Please buy a fridge with a lock.
Well...
I'll think about it...
since our lives may depend on it.
Hm?
Well then! We'd better
catch something for Sanji.
Hey, any luck fishing?
W-Well...
I feel lucky...
I seriously can't turn
my back for a second!
Ahh... I'm starving.
The fish aren't biting at all.
Luffy! It's your fault!
I mean, you even ate the bait!
If we don't have bait,
the fish won't bite!
You ate some too!
That's... I only ate what was
stuck to the lid of the bait box.
Luffy. Usopp. Have you
caught anything?
Karoo! Oh, no!
He might catch us a shark.
I wanna catch a sea king.
Just what do you two think
you're doing to Karoo?!
What's that?
What the heck is that?
Maybe it's cotton candy.
I'll go get Nami!
Hmm?
Nami, it's urgent! Come see!
Ahh... don't worry.
It's nothing. It's just steam.
Steam is coming up from the sea?
Yeah. It's a hot spot.
What the heck is that?
It's an area where magma spews.
There's an undersea volcano
below that area.
Oh?
A volcano even though it's undersea?
That's right. There are more volcanoes
under the water than above it.
Whoa...
Who cares? We can't eat it.
With an active volcano here,
a new island will be born
over thousands—
or tens of thousands—of years.
You're so cool, Nami!
Tens of thousands of years...
I wonder if I can live that long.
Nah, humans don't live that long.
Caught anything yet?
Oh, Sanji. I'm hungry.
Cook something.
You guys are hopeless.
I'll go upturn the storage
to see if anything's left.
Gah! It reeks of sulfur!
We can't see a thing
with steam everywhere!
Bear with it. We should
be through it soon.
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
What is it?!
There's smoke at twelve o'clock!
So what?! Sail right through it!
Yes, sir! Going in!
What's with the fog?
We can't see far!
We got through!
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei is gone!
Check inside!
We can't find him!
Can't be!
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Whoa...!
Aw, poop!
This duck came from out of nowhere,
and I jumped to it?!
– Is he a human?
– Dunno...
Oh?! Wahhh!
Help me! Please!
I can't swim! I can't swi–
I thought I'd die...
Well... I'm very swan-swan.
"Bon Kurei"
To think that I was saved
by pirates who are total strangers...
I will never forget your kindness!
Also, may I have
a cup of warm soup?
– Like we have it!
We're the ones who are hungry!
Oh! Hey there, you!
Aren't you just the cutest?!
Totally my type!
I could just eat you up!
What a weirdo...
So you can't swim, huh?
That's right. I ate a devil fruit.
Really? What kind of fruit?
Well, well... All we can do now is
wait for my ship to come pick me up.
So perhaps I'll put on a little show.
Behold my power!
What are you...?!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Didn't I say this would be a "show"?
What?!
Nobody's clowning here!
He's me!
Surprised?! Surprised?! Surprised?!
If I touch my face
with my left hand...
See?! Back to normal!
This is the power
of the Clone-Clone Fruit!
Even his voice...
His body was also the same!
A-Amazing!
There!
Ah! Come to think of it,
I didn't have to knock you down.
Because look...!
All that's needed is
to touch your faces
with my right hand.
As you can see, I can
mimic anyone!
Bodies too!
Ouch!
Stop that!
Hey, are you all right?
Ow, ow, ow...
Oh, my... Unfortunately, that's all
I'm willing to show of my power.
You're the best! Show some more!
Ahh... Well... if you insist...
I guess I'll show more!
Yeah! Show it! Show it!
It's not that exciting.
Well then, I guess I'll show...
We wanna see! We wanna see!
Furthermore, I'm equipped
with a memory feature!
Here we go!
Whoa!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
Ridiculous!
Spin! Spin!
So, did you like my special talent?
It's rare for me to show it off.
Cool!
Nobody's clowning here!
Oh, whatever!
That's my ship!
Amazing! Amazing! He's...
Ciao!
"Bon Kurei"
It's already time to say
goodbye? What a shame.
– What?!
Please don't go!
Chin up, and don't be sad!
Every voyage contains
some farewells.
But... never forget this:
Friendship...
has nothing to do with how long
we've known each other.
Don't cry!
Let's meet again!
Now, let's go, boys!
Yes, sir! Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Mr. 2?!
So then he's...
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei!
Vivi! You've never seen him?!
No... I've never met
Mr. 2 or the Mr. 1 duo.
I don't know their powers, either.
Though I've heard rumors...
Supposedly, Mr. 2 is...
a lanky ballerina who talks
with an effeminate voice.
He always wears a swan coat
that displays "Bon Kurei" on its back.
– You should've noticed!
What's the matter, Vivi?
Among the faces that he pulled
from his past memories...
from his memory feature...
I saw my father's face...
the face of Alabasta's king,
Nefertari Cobra!
If, for example,
you could mimic a king,
you could get away
with just about anything.
We let a troublesome
guy slip away, huh?
So he was our enemy?
He's one hell of a problem
if he's on the opposing side.
If he realizes that we're his enemies...
If he transforms into one of us
using his memory feature,
we won't be able to trust
our own friends.
You sure?
Listen, Luffy–
Wait. Hold it.
While it's true we might just be
going off Luffy's gut feeling,
I believe he's right to think
we don't need to be scared of him.
It's a stroke of luck
that we met up with him...
because now we'll outsmart him.
Mr. 2 Bon Kurei is...
Un, deux, trois!
What's "four" again?
somehow in a very good mood.
I made some new friends today!
Sea Cat (Sea Monster)
Territory: The Coast of Sandy Island
Something popped up!
A sea cat!
It's a sea monster!
It's our first meal in four days!
It's food!
We're on the right track.
I hope we get there soon.
Food!
Whoa! It's backing away!
Go back! Full reverse!
W-W-W-W-W-W-We can't!
Oh!
Don't let it get away!
We have to capture it!
Now, how would you like
to be cooked, cat monster?!
You can't!
Vivi! You jerk! What are you doing?!
Wh... Why... Vivi?
You can't eat it!
Sea cats are a sacred
animal in Alabasta!
Tell us sooner!
The sea's full of all kinds of creatures!
You've got a ways to go if you're
scared of things like that.
Okay then!
Here's a story all about how I bravely
fought off sea kings in the Calm Belt.
Fought off sea kings?!
Big ones! They were this big!
O-Our food got away...
It will all be okay! You'll soon
have plenty to fill your belly!
Really?! What kind of cat
will appear next time?!
Vivi! The wind and weather
seem to be stabilizing.
Yes.
We've entered
Alabasta's climate area.
A sea cat appearing
is a sure sign, too.
And just look behind us.
More proof Alabasta's
close by, right?
There are so many ships!
When did that happen?!
Hey! They're all flying
Baroque Works' colors!
Its employees have started gathering.
They're most likely the billions,
the officer agents' subordinates.
Then there are at least
200 men out there.
In point of fact, they're
the 200 elites of Baroque Works.
The bounty hunters at
Whisky Peak don't even compare.
Should we fire at them
while we can?!
Let's get the drop on them!
It's quicker if we go
there and beat them up!
No, wait! We gotta eat first!
It'd be dumb to bother
with those small-timers.
He's right.
If we lose sight of our
real target, we're done for.
And there are only eight of us.
Just... tie it tightly.
Our enemy this time
is overly secretive.
Perfect.
These will help us tell
who our real crewmates are.
Does that Clone-Clone Fruit guy really
become so similar
when he transforms?
Seeing is believing!
It's not just "similar,"
it's identical!
It's too bad! You should've seen it.
We even danced with him.
Knowing someone like that
is among our enemy,
we can't carelessly act alone.
Hey, what should I do?
Ahh... Do what you can do.
You don't have to do anything more.
It's okay to run away from
an enemy you can't defeat!
Are you talking to him or yourself?
What I can do, huh?
Got it!
I can see the island now!
We'll visit Nanohana, that town ahead,
but we need to hide the ship.
Alright! So, no matter what happens,
our left arms prove
that we're definitely crewmates!
Now, let's get ashore!
To a restaurant!
Oh, and to Alabasta.
– As a side note?
Our enemy this time is
a group of assassins, Luffy.
Yeah. That's right.
Be careful about acting
on instinct, okay?
You're right. I got it.
Yeah! That's right! Yeah! Got it!
The Port of Nanohana,
The Kingdom of Alabasta
Hey! What's going on?
What happened?
Oh. It seems someone
keeled over in that restaurant.
Keeled over?!
He seems to have died in the middle
of a conversation with the proprietor!
He's an out-of-towner.
We think he unwittingly ate
a desert strawberry while traveling.
A desert strawberry?
They're poisonous spiders that
look like red strawberries.
Eat one by accident, and you'll
suddenly drop dead a few days later.
Contagious poison spreads through
the corpse for a few hours after that,
so nobody can get close.
In the desert, what you
don't know can kill you.
Just look! The way he's stuck
in that position, still holding the meat,
is proof of just how powerful
the desert strawberry's poison is!
He came back to life!
A-Are you all right?
Oh, my bad.
I dozed off.
– That was dozing off?!
R-Ridiculous! You were in the middle
of a conversation and a meal!
And he's right back to eating!
So what's the big fuss?
– We were worried you'd died!
Is this restaurant known
for comedy routines?
No, it's not like that.
But we're glad you're okay.
– Hey! Don't just pass out again!
Huh? So he wasn't really dead?
Just a false alarm.
That hit the spot!
Say, Mister...
Yeah?!
You seen this guy in town?
He's a pirate with a straw hat...
You've got a lot of guts
eating out in public,
Second Division commander
of the Whitebeard Pirates...
Commander Portgas D. Ace
Second Division
Whitebeard Pirates
Commander Portgas D. Ace
Second Division
Whitebeard Pirates
Commander Portgas D. Ace
Second Division
Whitebeard Pirates
Portgas D. Ace.
Wh-Whitebeard?!
The Whitebeard Pirates?!
That numbskull is one of
the Whitebeard Pirates?!
You know, I recognize
the tattoo on his back!
That's the mark
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
What's he doing here?!
What's a famous, big-shot pirate
doing in this country?
Just looking...
for my kid brother!